傲骨之战
第一季 第四集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
公告     人人视频[人人美剧]盗用本组名号  请抵制
翻译      Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  吃冰棒  ABCpril
翻译      dzysteven  杨爱菜  一点都不酷喵  胡说大王  半半子七
校对      free维塔  某羽
时间轴      Avis  西·查  噃噃
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free维塔
最新海外影视剧下载
鬼混名单
试试水浴式罐头
Try a water bath canner.
你在说什么
I'm sorry?
食品酸性较低  比一般罐头要好
For low acid foods. It's better than a regular pot.
相信我
Trust me.
不  都是瞎掰
No, that's crazy.
只是含糖量较低而已
Just reduce the sugar content.
玛娅  我们有一个生育案
Maia, we have a fertility case.
家庭法  重要客户
Uh, family law. Important client.
好  知道了
Okay, good.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事  在电梯发生了一段奇怪的对话
Yeah. Just weird conversation in the elevator.
需要我做什么
Um, what do you need?
找到和生育诊所返还条款有关的所有先例
Uh, all precedences on fertility clinic reversion clauses.
好  我马上去办
Good. I'm on it.
如果有人说你坏话记得告诉我
And tell me if you're getting some bad-mouthing.
-有人说我坏话  -人们都喜欢八卦
- If I'm getting...? - Well, people say things.
有时人们就是闲的没事干
You know, sometimes people don't know better.
什么  你听到什么了吗
What, is someone saying something?
没有  除了你所说的以外
No. I mean, no more than what you said.
我说了什么
What did I say?
卢卡
Lucca.
这不是你的推特  对吗
It's not your Twitter feed, is it?
什么
What?
这不是你的推特消息
It's not your Twitter feed.
我感觉我错过了什么
I feel like I'm missing something here.
"当人们在背后喊你蕾丝时
"It's hard to get excited about work
你很难在工作中打起精神"
when people call you lesbo behind your back."
我的天  什么
Oh, my God. What?
写着你的名字  你看  玛娅·林德尔
Yeah, it's your name. See? Maia Rindell.
你提到了你的家人  你父亲锒铛入狱
And you talk about your parents and your dad going to jail...
玛娅·林德尔
爸爸的小蕾丝  热爱生活  永不改变  及时行乐
可是我
But I...
这不是我
That's not me.
那换我的话就会找人谈谈
Well, then I'd talk to someone,
因为  你看
because, I mean, look.
"我最喜欢桃子罐头
"I love canning peaches best.
有谁知道为什么它们总黏在罐头边吗"
Anyone know why they stick to the side?"
-怎么回事  -你真的很喜欢水果罐头
- What on earth? - Yeah, you're really into canning fruit.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
是谁干的
Who's doing this?
我的天
Oh, my God.
当我给我女朋友口交时  那里犹如一片湿地
你的风格很十八禁
Yeah, you get pretty explicit.
"当我给我女朋友口交时..."
"When I go down on my girlf..."
我的天
Oh, my God.
没错  你有一大批粉丝
Yeah. You have a lot of fans, too.
-标签"湿地"  -这是
- #Wetlands. - This is...
谁干的
Who's doing this?
我不知道  你和谁有仇吗
I don't know. Do you have any enemies?
都是丑闻惹的祸
It's the scandal.
是我父母的丑闻惹的祸
It's my parents' scandal.
我该怎么做
What do I do?
-给她回推  -什么
- Tweet back to her. - What?
看看她会不会回复你
Yeah, see if she says anything.
或许你能发现她到底是谁
Maybe you can find out who she is.
来  用我的账号
Here, use my account.
"我是同性恋  我也喜欢罐头
"I'm gay and like canning, too.
我们应该见上一面"
We should meet up."
我想把我的卵子拿回来
I want my eggs back.
好
Okay.
被谁拿走了
And who has them?
湖道生育诊所
The Lake Drive Fertility Clinic.
劳拉  这是我们的新晋合伙人
Laura, this is our newest partner,
戴安·洛哈特
Diane Lockhart.
戴安  这位是劳拉·萨勒诺
Diane, this is Laura Salano,
我们最老的客户之一
one of our oldest clients.
"最老的"   肯定有更好听的词来形容吧
"Oldest"? My God, there's got to be - a better word than that.
最早的客户  不好意思
First clients, sorry.
最早也是最好的
First and best.
好多了
Oh, better.
所以当我第一次来这儿时
So when I first moved here,
我需要钱  记得吗
I needed money, remember?
有对高地公园的夫妇出价两万买我的卵子
And some Highland Park couple gave me $20,000 for my eggs.
-合同是由我们拟定的  对吗  -没错
- We drew up that contract, right? - Yes.
我记得你说过里面有些关于
And I remember you said there was some boilerplate
返还条款的说明
in there about a reversion clause.
如果他们几年内没用卵子
If they didn't use the eggs in a few years, um...
"如果想要植入成型胚胎
"If the intended parents'
有意怀孕的夫妇
desire to gestate the resulting embryos
湖道生育诊所
在五年限期内仍未完成者  所有卵子
to term is not completed within five years, then all ova,
将归还于捐赠者  属其个人财产"
henceforth known as 'property' will revert back to donor."
没错  就是这样
Good, exactly.
所以已经八年了  它们是我的了  对吗
So it's been eight years; they're mine, right?
没错  合同是这么写的
Yes, according to the contract.
我们得告知他们一下
We just need to notify them.
我今天就去通知他们
Oh, I'll get on it today.
你有植入的想法吗
Are you planning to implant?
我想要个孩子
I want a child.
从去年三月  从这次惊吓之后
After last March, after this-this scare,
我  之前觉得这不可能了
I... didn't think I'd get to this moment.
-你现在好起来了  -没错
- And you're well now? - Yes.
卵巢癌
Um, ovarian cancer.
但我现在没有健康问题了
But I have a clean bill of health,
我只是怀不了小孩
and I just can't get pregnant.
所以这些卵子  就是我唯一的希望
So these eggs, they're my only chance.
只是很好奇你现在把重心转移了
It's just weird how your priorities change.
我很抱歉  我现在听着像卫生棉广告一样
I'm sorry, I sound like a tampon commercial right now.
我会尽我所能
Well, let me see what I can do.
谢谢你  戴安
Thanks, Diane.
所以你们是在扩张吗
So you're expanding?
天呐
Girl...
快解释
Explain.
那人是谁
Who was that?
那个男的
That man?
不知道  要我去弄清楚吗
I don't know. Want me to find out?
是的
Yes.
不  等等
Uh, no, wait.
别进博斯曼先生的办公室
Don't go into Mr. Boseman's office.
你没事吧
You all right?
没事  抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
好的
All right.
迈克·克里斯特瓦
Mike Kresteva.
-你确定吗  -我可以再回去确认
- You sure? - I can go back.
不用
No, no.
他到这儿来做什么
What is he doing here?
不知道  我可以问问
I don't know. I can ask.
不用  梅丽莎  等等
No, uh, Marissa, wait.
不  好吧
No... Okay.
告诉阿德里安  我得和他谈谈
Tell Adrian I need to talk to him.
看来我们没法让他...
Can't seem to get him...
戴安要和你谈谈
Diane needs a word with you.
现在吗
Now?
失陪一下
Excuse me.
怎么了
What's wrong?
迈克·克里斯特瓦
Mike Kresteva.
他来这儿做什么
What's he doing here?
不知道  我们还没聊到那儿
I don't know. We hadn't gotten that far yet.
你认识他吗
You know him?
我原来律所里的一个合伙人
One of the partners at my firm,
艾丽西娅·福瑞克认识他
Alicia Florrick, knew him.
他让她过得生不如死
He made her life hell.
好吧
Okay.
你打断我们谈话还有什么具体原因吗
Is there some specific reason you needed to - interrupt the meeting?
小心点  阿德里安
Be careful, Adrian.
我是说真的  他可不坦率
Seriously. He's not straight-forward.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你  戴安
Thank you, thank you, Diane.
但是
But...
我能应付
I can handle myself.
要我做什么吗
Want me to do something?
是的  打给湖道生育诊所
Oh, yes, uh, get Lake Drive Fertility Clinic on the line.
请问有何贵干  克里斯特瓦先生
So what can I do for you, Mr. Kresteva?
我刚被任命为特别法律顾问
Well, I was just made Special Counsel
负责司法部警察问责司事务
in charge of the Department of Justice Police Accountability
隶属21世纪专案组
in the 21st Century Task Force.
这头衔够长的
That's a mouthful.
没错
Yeah, it is.
我还省略了芝加哥三个字
And I even left out the word "Chicago."
司法部警责司21世纪专案组
D.O.J.P.A.T.C.T.F.
在寻求建议
have been asked for recommendations
来约束芝加哥的警察暴力执法
on how to curb police brutality in Chicago.
你可以先把施暴的警察都关进监狱
Well, you could start by putting brutal cops in jail.
我为什么就没想到这点呢
Now, why didn't I think of that?
有回复了吗
Nothing yet?
还没
Not yet.
是不是应该再发一条
Should we write again?
不  那样会显得太饥渴了
No, we'll sound desperate.
我们已经提过想见面了
We already suggested we meet.
怎么了
What?
她回复了
She tweeted back.
-什么  -"你长什么样  标签'湿地之交'"
- What?! - "What do you look like? #Wetlandsex"
给我看你的  我就给你看我的
你要怎么回
What are you gonna say?
-我要发张照片  -你的照片吗
- I'll send a photo. - What, of you?
不是  我有个照片库
No, I have a photo stream.
没人会发自己的照片发出去
No one sends photos of themselves.
用这张吧
Here's one.
叫她发张回来
Ask her to send a photo back.
调查员叫什么
Uh, what's the investigator's name?
杰·迪佩西亚  要我去叫他吗
Jay DiPersia. Want me to get him?
对  再叫上卢卡
Yes, and Lucca, too.
什么  梅丽莎
What... Marissa?
你有新消息
You got something.
回得挺快
That was fast.
你也发了附件
Wow, you sent an attachment too.
你是个放荡的姑娘
You're a saucy wench.
怎么了
What?
照片上是我
That's me.
真的吗  你知道谁拍的吗
Really? Do you know who took them?
戴安·洛哈特
Diane Lockhart.
迈克·克里斯特瓦
Mike Kresteva.
这就像是以前一样
Well, this feels like old times.
你今天又是什么说辞  迈克
And what line are you selling today, Mike?
为什么所有人都在怀疑我
Why is everybody so suspicious of me?
我才进你办公室  什么都还没说
I just walked into your office, I haven't even said anything.
那就快说
So say something.
好吧
Okay.
我是站在你这边的
I'm on your side.
而那又是哪边
And what side is that?
约束警察暴力执法的那边
The side hoping to curb police brutality.
我被任命为特别法律顾问了
I've just been made special counsel.
不错  恭喜你
Good. Congratulations.
这可有够真诚的  有建议吗
That was genuine. Any advice?
没有
No.
戴安  我想你会意识到我已经变了
Diane, I think you'll learn that I've changed.
我已经重新做人了
I'm a new person.
你儿子怎么样了  迈克
How is your son doing, Mike?
他  他去世了
Well, he, uh... passed.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
大概一年前的事了
Yeah. About a year ago.
急性淋巴细胞白血病
Acute lymphoblastic leukemia.
别担心  他走的时候没有痛苦
Don't worry, he wasn't in pain or anything.
他高中毕业了
And he got to graduate high school,
那也是他的梦想
which was his dream.
拿到了毕业证书
Got a diploma.
那是他一生中最自豪的时刻
It was the proudest moment of his life.
迈克  我...
Mike, I...
真是太遗憾了  我简直难以想象
I'm so sorry. I-I can't imagine.
他想要的  不过是让这个世界更好一些
All he wanted was to make the world a better place.
这就是我做这份工作的原因
That's why I took this job.
如果我们能让警察暴力执法的案件不再发生
And if we can stop police brutality cases,
那将会是一个很好的开始  对吗
then that's a pretty good start, right?
总之
Anyway...
如果你改变主意  请你告诉我
let me know if you change your mind.
迈克·克里斯特瓦之子的死亡
查查网
雅各布·克里斯特瓦(1998-2016)
生育诊所遇上一个问题
A problem with the fertility clinic...
他们说没有
they say they have no record
劳拉·萨勒诺的捐赠记录
of a Laura Salano ever donating there.
戴安·洛哈特  请进
Diane Lockhart, please.
洛哈特女士  我们不确定能否帮到您
I'm, uh, not sure how we can help you, Ms. Lockhart.
到了一定年龄之后  生育能力...
At a certain age, fertility...
我不是为我自己来的
I'm not here for myself.
我是为一个客户来的
I'm here for a client.
你是卵子经纪人吗
Oh. You're an egg broker?
不  我是一名律师
No, a lawyer.
你以前是湖道生育诊所的吧  医生
Uh, you used to be the Lake Drive Fertility Clinic, Doctor?
是的  好几年前
Yes, years ago.
事实上是两年前
Actually, two years ago.
好的  我还是会说好几年前
Okay. I would call that years ago.
湖道在财务上遇到了麻烦  而我们没有
Lake Drive had financial troubles. We don't.
再问一下  我能帮你做些什么
How may I help you again?
我们代表当事人劳拉·萨勒诺前来拜访
Uh, we called on behalf our client, Laura Salano.
贵所库存中有她的12个卵子
You have 12 eggs of hers in storage.
实际上  是在我们所替代的
Actually, that was Lake Drive who had them in storage,
湖道生育诊所的库存里
the fertility clinic we replaced.
你说的那家诊所跟贵所在同一幢建筑里
You mean the fertility clinic in the same building,
用同一个医疗主任  也就是你
with the same medical director... you?
是的
Yes.
你还需要别的什么吗  女士
Is there anything else you might need, ma'am?
那些卵子的地点
The location of the eggs.
合同是跟湖道签的
You see, this contract was with Lake Drive.
自湖道关门之日起就无效了
It was voided the day Lake Drive closed its doors.
不  先生  这合同要求如果你们关门停业
No, sir. This contract required that you contact our client
要事先联系我们的当事人
if ever you were to close your doors.
那些卵子都已经不在了
Well, the eggs are gone.
我们重新开业的时候清理了整个系统
We flushed out the system when we reopened.
那你就等着我们的传票吧
Then you can expect our filing.
等等  等等  我们没做错什么
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wai... We did nothing wrong here.
你可以随便告湖道  但不能告我们
You're welcome to sue Lake Drive, but not us.
不  我们起诉你  针对个人起诉  医生
No, we will be suing you, personally, Doctor.
你掌管一家设施相同
You are in charge of a clinic
医疗主任相同的诊所
with the same facilities and same director?
我猜你是不想让州政府办公室
My guess is you don't want the secretary of state's office
好好查查欺诈转移
looking closely into a fraudulent transfer.
好吧  等下
Okay, hold on.
劳拉
Laura?
萨勒诺
Salano.
卵子捐赠给芝加哥理工大学
基因研究实验室(人道主义)
找到了
Okay.
出于人道主义原因  那些卵子被送到了
They were sent to Chicago Poly-Tech
芝加哥理工大学
for humanitarian reasons.
你是因为失误  卵子到这来了
You're saying the ovum ended up here by mistake?
-是的  湖道送过来的  -你说啥
- Yes, from Lake Drive. - Pardon?
从湖道生育诊所送过来的
Uh, from Lake Drive Fertility.
是意外捐赠的
It was donated accidentally.
你想知道它们现在在哪里
Ah. And you want to know where they are.
查查吧
Well, let's see.
是的  它们送到我们的干细胞研究实验室了
Yes, they were transferred to our stem cell research lab.
很好  实验室在哪儿
Good. Where is that?
-实验室在哪  -你在那里是找不到它们的
- Where is that? - Oh, you won't find them still there.
他们已经受精了并且丢销了
No, they've already been fertilized and D&Ded.
丢销
D&Ded?
是的  丢弃并销毁
Yeah, discarded and destroyed.
11个全都是
All 11 of them.
对不起
I'm sorry.
等等  应该有12个
Wait, there were 12.
不  11个  一共11个
No, 11, there were 11...
不  一共捐了12个
No, there were 12 donated.
第12个卵子在哪里
Where is the 12th egg?
被标为"保密"了
Ah, it's marked "Confidential."
什么  什么保密
What? What is?
卵子
The egg.
你能明白我说的话吗
Can you understand what I'm saying?
有时候我自己都听不清我自己说什么
Sometimes I find it difficult to hear myself.
不  我能听清
No, I can hear you.
可是你们是公共机构啊  医生
But you're a public institution, Doctor;
为什么会标为保密呢
why is it marked confidential?
不  看上去不像下雨的样子
No, it doesn't look like rain.
所以  我的卵子有一个还在
So, one of my eggs still exists,
但是我们不知道在哪里
but we don't know where?
是的  它被列为保密内容了
Yes, it was listed as confidential.
-但是其他的都没了  -是的
- But none of the others were? - No.
他们为什么要藏起来一个
Why would they keep one egg hidden?
病人隐私
Patient confidentiality?
理工大学里的研究员有没有给患者治疗的
Do any of the Poly-Tech researchers see patients?
我不能告诉你  那被列为保密信息了
I can't tell you. It's listed as confidential.
你能不能至少告诉我们
Can you at least tell us
哪些带教医生接诊患者
which teaching doctors see patients?
什么
What?
你能告诉我们哪些医生接诊患者吗
Can you tell us which doctors see patients?
谢谢你们
Oh, thank you,
但是还没到午饭时间呢
but it's not lunchtime yet.
你知道我们是律师吗  医生
Do you know we're lawyers, Doctor?
你说什么
Pardon?
你知道我们是律师吗
Do you know that we're lawyers?
没什么  感谢你的帮助
Never mind. Thanks for your help.
十月
October.
芝加哥理工大学
人类基因研究院
理查德·诺伍德
人类基因组研究
诺伍德医生  你所拥有的一颗卵子
The ovum that you have, Dr. Norwood,
是归我们的客户所有  现在她想把它要回来
it belongs to our client, and she wants it back.
你们有什么证据
What's your evidence of that?
这份合同
This contract.
这上面承认了湖道接收了12颗卵子
This acknowledgement of the transfer of 12 eggs from Lake Drive.
基因组实验室承认了他们将其中一颗
The Genome labs acknowledgement
转到了你这里
that they transferred one egg to you.
你们要这颗卵子干什么
And why do you want the ovum?
她需要她的卵子怀孕
She needs her egg back to fertilize it.
很遗憾  这恐怕...
Regrettably, here's the problem...
你已经把卵子摧毁了
You've already destroyed it?
不  我们已经让它受精了
No, we've already fertilized it.
再笑一下
One more smile.
好的
Okay.
再笑一下
One more smile.
看着妈妈
Look at Mom.
再笑一下
Just one more smile.
如果要我说话就尽管开口
Tell me if you need me to say anything,
因为我站在一旁就很能吓唬人
because I could just stand here being intimidating,
像这样皱着眉头
you know, frowning like this.
很好  很好  保持微笑
Great. That's great. Now, keep smiling.
看着我  头稍微向左偏一点
Look at me. Just turn your head a little bit to the left.
等我一下  马上就回来
Just give me a second. I'll be right back.
你想怎样
What do you want?
你不要再骚扰我了
I want you to stop harassing me.
我什么都没干
I'm not doing anything.
-你们进了我的店  -别装了  泰德
- You came into my shop. - Stop pretending, Ted.
那上面有你拍的照片
It has your photographs,
我让你拍的我的照片
the photographs I let you take of me.
你把照片放到了...
You linked them to...
好吧  玛娅  我不知道你在说什么
Okay, Maia, I don't know what the hell you're talking about,
要不你先预约一下...
but why don't you make an appointment...
她想现在和你谈谈
She wants to talk to you now.
这是你的新女友吗
So this is your new girlfriend?
不是  但这没关系
No, but that shouldn't matter.
我不是拉拉  但我也可以是
I mean, I'm not gay, but I could be.
这是骚扰  泰德
It's harassment, Ted.
我是律师  我可以告得你倾家荡产
I'm a lawyer, and I could sue you for everything you have.
你是说这些吗
Oh, you mean all of this?
我们的事已经过去四年了  放手吧
It was four years ago. Get over it.
我已经放手了  我认识了别人
I am over it; I met someone,
不管你觉得我现在是在干什么...
so whatever it is that you think that I'm doing...
希望能早点见到你
这些照片只有你有  泰德
You're the only one who had these photos, Ted.
这是推特机器人发的
It's a Twitterbot.
-天啊  -我两年前放上去的
- Oh, Jesus. - I got it up and running two years ago.
只不过现在因为庞氏骗局才有人关注
It's just getting attention now because of the Ponzi scheme.
什么是推特机器人
What's a Twitterbot?
一个可以生成推特消息的程序
It's a program that imitates a Twitter feed.
为什么是对水果罐头感兴趣
That's why the interest in canning fruit?
它被设定表现出某种有特殊癖好的人的特性
It's programed to take on characteristics of hobbyists sites.
增添点个性
Adds personality.
好吧  关掉它
Okay, so turn it off.
如果是你发明了这个机器人  把它关掉
If you invented this bot, turn it off.
如果我关闭了  它也会自我复制
If I try to kill it, it'll just duplicate itself.
它在假扮我
It's pretending to be me.
别理它就行了
So just ignore it.
你真是个混蛋
You're an asshole.
是你把我甩了
Hey, you're the one who broke up with me.
要你女朋友去解决吧
Tell your girlfriend to fix it.
这样很成熟  玛娅  非常成熟
It's very adult, Maia... it's very adult!
是啊  我女朋友可不是好惹的
Yeah, my girlfriend's pretty tough.
洛哈特女士  林德尔女士
Ms. Lockhart. Ms. Rindell.
-什么事  -什么事
- Yes? - Yes?
你们被传唤了
You've been served.
-有人找我吗  -博斯曼先生
- Somebody here for me? - Mr. Boseman.
-什么事  -你被传唤了
- Yeah? - You've been served.
不是吧  逗我呢
Come on, you kidding me?
-谁传唤我们的  -克里斯特瓦
- By who? - Kresteva.
你们能告诉我卢卡·奎恩女士
And can one of you point me in the direction
在哪里吗
of a Ms. Lucca Quinn?
祝你们在大陪审团前好运
Good luck with the grand jury.
雷迪克&博斯曼律所
民事案件传票
-你要我说多久  -20分钟
- How long do you want me to say? - 20 minutes.
说还有个非现做的
You got a backup.
懂了
Got it.
他们来了
Here they come.
来个八盎司的汉堡  多加洋葱
Eight-ouncer, Mike, extra onions.
你有多少时间
How long you got?
15分钟  法官今天心情不好
15. Judge is not happy.
做这个要20分钟  还有个非现做的
It'll take 20. I got a backup.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
这不是法律  是汉堡  做汉堡需要时间
Hey, it's not justice, it's burgers; they take time.
多加洋葱和胡椒
Extra onions, peppers?
当然
Of course.
算了  迈克
Forget it, Mike.
你在这等了我一整天吗
So, what, you've been waiting in here all day for me to come in?
是  你的魅力无人能挡
Yep, your charm is that irresistible.
你想知道我在想什么吗
You want to know what I think?
迫不及待想知道
Can't wait.
我觉得你迫不及待要在见我一面
I think you couldn't wait to see me again,
所以你的汉堡已经切成两半了
and that's why the burger's already cut in half.
被你发现了
You got me.
这可真是个坏习惯  你说呢
This is a bad habit, isn't it?
你挑逗我
You teasing me,
我笑一笑  再挑逗回去
me grinning and teasing you back?
很容易
It's easy.
那什么不容易
As opposed to?
实话
The truth?
有点意思  继续
This should be interesting. Go.
去年  我看了心理医生
Last year, I went to see a, uh, therapist.
吉尔伯特医生
Dr. Gilbert.
因为我恋爱从来不会超过
My problem was that my relationships never lasted
三个星期
more than three weeks.
我想知道是我的问题还是她们的问题
I wanted to know if the problem was me or them.
那肯定是她们的了
Oh, it has to be them.
吉尔伯特医生说因为我的生活太过轻松
Well, Dr. Gilbert said that the ease of my life
导致我总是浅尝辄止
had made me treat things superficially,
所以我需要从我最爱的东西开始
and that what I needed to do was refrain
控制我自己
from the thing that I loved the most
保持一整年
for a full year.
真是胡扯
God, this is such shit.
不  我说的每个字都是真的
No, every word I'm telling you is the truth.
三月十四日  晚上八点半
At 8:30 p.m., on March 14th,
这一年就结束了
the year will be up.
所以你在找一个
And you're looking for someone
和你分享这段深刻经历的人
to share this deep experience with you?
没错  你尽管笑吧
Yeah. Laugh if you will,
我需要一个女人
but I need a woman
会喜欢我所...
who is able to enjoy what I have...
一个能分享你的床
Someone to share your bed with,
让你知道真爱的意义的人吗
someone to show you the true meaning of love?
不  天哪  才不要
No, God, no.
我在找一个可以在斯库特蛋奶冻店里
No, I'm looking for someone to share a milkshake
和我分享奶昔的人
at Scooter's Frozen Custard.
这一年绝对很难熬
No, been a very long, hard year.
那家店的奶昔真是绝了
God, they are good.
性不过一时欢愉  但波士顿风味奶昔...
Sex is transient, but a Boston Shake...
所以你是邀请我吗
Okay, am I being invited?
正是
Yeah.
下周二
Next Tuesday.
然后我们就可以来一炮了
Afterwards we could have sex.
这是什么
What's this?
这是
It's a subpoena
司法部给我和律所发的传票
authorized by the D.O.J. for me and my firm.
你今天来就是为了这个
So is this why you came in here today?
没错
Yes.
科林  我找你
As fascinating as I find you, Colin,
就是想知道迈克·克里斯特瓦的目的
I need to know what Mike Kresteva's up to.
克里斯特瓦搞的
This is from Kresteva?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
他刚被分配负责警察暴力相关的案件
Well, he was just given the police brutality study.
我知道  但他为什么盯上我们
Yes. So why is he after us?
不知道
I don't know.
我会查清楚的
I'll check it out.
谢谢你的汉堡
Thanks for the burger.
不用
You're welcome.
你出卖我  迈克
You sold me out, Mike.
我想我帮上忙了
Okay, I think I helped here.
-那个推特账号吗  -是的
- With the Twitter account? - Yeah.
刚才是你第一次扇别人耳光吗
Was that the first time you ever slapped anyone?
大概是吧
Yeah, I guess it was.
我联系了推特管理员  告诉他们
Anyway, I contacted Twitter and told them
是推特机器人在冒充你
it was a Twitterbot imitating you,
他们冻结了那个账户  之后会再核实身份
and they froze it until they review it.
太棒了
That's great.
我都没想到还有这个办法
I didn't even realize you could do that.
我也是
I didn't either.
劳拉  问题是...
The, uh, problem, Laura, is...
仅剩的卵子也已经受精了
the last remaining ova has already been fertilized.
是谁
By who?
这就是问题所在
That's the question.
我们不知道
We don't know.
我们查出它被存放在芝加哥理工大学的
We located it at Chicago Poly-Tech,
遗传学实验室
in the genetics lab,
我们会将他们告上法庭
and we're bringing them to court.
这个案子是不错  不过...
There might be a good case here, but...
你想为此打官司吗
do you want to fight it?
毕竟你知道孩子的生父已无从选择
Knowing that you won't be able to choose the genetic father.
你的卵子也已被他受精
Your ova has already been fertilized by someone.
一个你可能与之对簿公堂的人
Someone you may have to fight.
搞什么鬼
What a load of shit.
霍夫女士  每次见面都这么愉快
Ms. Hoff, always good to see you.
她真的不在乎父亲是谁吗
She really doesn't care who the father is?
劳拉  让律师处理
Laura, this should be between the lawyers.
我猜你是代表整个家庭咯
My guess is you're representing the family?
我代表受精卵的拥有者
Mm, I'm representing the owners of the fertilized embryo.
不  你只代表这颗受精卵的
No, you're representing the co-owner
共同拥有者之一
of the fertilized embryo.
我们则代表另一位
We are representing the other co-owner.
她卖出卵子的那一刻就已经放弃了所有权
She abandoned ownership when she sold her eggs.
但有合同为证  她保留了所有权
Contractually, she retained ownership.
我的客户对那份合同完全不知情
My clients knew nothing of that contract.
但这也否认不了合同的存在
That doesn't negate that contract.
对于我的客户而言  就是如此
As far as my clients are concerned, it does.
你应该去告致使合同无效的人...
Your beef is with whoever voided the contract...
还好吗
Everything all right?
没事  我只想看看父亲是谁
Yeah, yeah, I just want to see who the dad is.
他会坐在被告席对吗
He'll be on the other side, right?
是的
I think so.
下一个进那扇门的人
The next person through those doors
就是我孩子的父亲
will be the father of my child.
下一个进那扇门的男性就是我孩子的父亲
The next male through those doors will be the father of my child.
我的客户会支付
My client is willing to pay
-你们寻找另一位卵子捐赠者的费用  -真大方
- for you to find another egg donor. - How gracious.
-他们对现在这个就很满意  -拜托
- They are happy with this one. - Oh, come on.
他们还有其他机会  而她只有这一个卵子了
They have other opportunities. She just has this one egg.
你的委托人尚可以让很多卵子受精
Your client can fertilize a lot of eggs.
而且我们愿意支付18500美元
And we're willing to offer $18,500
给其他卵子捐赠者
to pay for another egg donor.
这家人花了很多年时间才找到一位适格捐赠者
This family has spent years looking for a donor.
我们会付钱让他们去找另一位的
And we will pay for them to find another.
为什么一定要是这一个呢
Why does this one matter?
你在想什么
What do you think?
我觉得那就是我孩子的父亲
I think that's the father to my baby.
这场官司你想继续打下去吗
Do you want to keep fighting?
我打算抚养一个孩子并送他去上大学
There's a kid I plan to raise and send to college.
18年后  他或者她会是我的孩子
18 years from now, he or she will be mine.
我才是抚养他长大成人的最佳人选
I don't see anybody else raising him.
很好  我们就需要你这个决心
Good. That's what we need to hear.
全体起立
All rise!
请各位就坐
Let's all take our seats please.
我读过你们的案情陈述了
I've read your briefs.
我知道双方对此案热情都很高
I know there's a lot of passion...
蒂莫西·斯坦内克法官  家事法庭
让我看下你的手机
Let me see your phone.
不是我的手机  法官阁下
It's... it's not my phone, Your Honor.
是这块表
It's, uh... it's this watch.
让我看一下
Let me see it.
好的
Yeah, yeah.
这只是个
It's just a... just a...
该...  法官阁下
Oh, sh... Your Honor?
原告希望
The, uh, plaintiff would like
对本案的卵子植入手术施行紧急禁止是吗
an emergency injunction against implantation?
是的  法官阁下  卵子的所有权上有争议
Yes, Your Honor. There is some question about the ownership.
原告在以两万美元售出
The plaintiff relinquished ownership
她的卵子之时就已经放弃了所有权
when she sold her ova for $20,000.
不  她在卵子售出五年后拥有
No, she has contractual control
契约处置权
after five years.
我的委托人对那份合同毫不知情
My clients knew nothing about that contract.
如果原告把她的车抵押给了第三方
If the plaintiff had loaned her car to a third party,
而第三方把这辆车卖给了我们
and that third party sold the car to us,
那么原告所提出的任何争议
the plaintiff's disagreement
都应针对那个第三方  而不是我们
is with the third party, not with us.
我们讨论的不是车
It's not a car,
法官阁下  这是一枚胚胎
Your Honor, this is an embryo.
一枚双亲共同拥有的胚胎
An embryo that is co-owned by two parents.
并不是双亲  那使其个人化了
Not two parents. That personalizes...
我的委托人的DNA
My client's DNA...
好了  好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay.
我将批准一份针对这项手术施行的
I will grant a temporary injunction against implantation
临时紧急禁止令以便让双方有时间呈上证据
merely to give both of you time to present evidence.
-请准备好证据于明天回到  -法官阁下
- Please return tomorrow ready to... - Your Honor,
我的委托人已经计划于下周前往英国
my clients have a... trip planned to England next week.
如果这案子对他们很重要  他们会留下来的
If this matters to them, they'll stay.
休庭
Adjourned.
抱歉  法官阁下  我能把手表拿回来了吗
Excuse me. Your Honor, can I have my watch back?
玛娅·林德尔  "丑闻之女"被律所解雇
喂
Hi.
喂  是我  叶莎
Hi. It's Yesha.
是这样的  我刚读到一篇文章
Yeah, I just read an article.
你是要被律所解雇了吗
Are you about to get fired?
什么
What?!
玛娅·林德尔  "丑闻之女"被解雇了
「美国新闻」上有篇文章坚称
There's an article on American News insisting
你被你的律所开除了
that you are being fired from your law firm.
什么  没有  为什么这么说
What?! No! Wh-Why?
上面写着你对反同性恋偏见提出的指责
Okay, it says that your accusations of anti-gay bias
激怒了你的上司
have angered your bosses.
等下  等等
Wait. Hold on.
进来
Yeah?
我被解雇了吗
Am I being fired?
什么事
What?
我被解雇了吗
Am I being fired?
我甚至都不知道你是谁
I barely even know who you are.
所以我没被解雇吗
So I'm not?
你没有
You're not.
走吧
Go.
谢谢
Thank you.
是个谎言  我没有被解雇
It's a lie. I'm not being fired.
我刚又收到个新谷歌快讯
I just got a new Google alert.
上面说你刚花了35万购买珠宝
It says that you just bought $350,000 in jewelry.
什么
What?! What?!
是我前男友干的  他又开始了
It's my ex-boyfriend. He's at it again.
大陪审团问询中
戴安  你好
Diane. Hi.
-你好  -感谢你出席
- Hello. - Thank you for appearing
今天的大陪审团问询
in front of our grand jury today.
不必谢我
No thanks are necessary.
我是被传唤的
I was subpoenaed.
-我别无选择  -总之
- I had no choice. - Well,
还是谢谢你
thank you, anyway.
我昨天是否去过你办公室
Did I visit your office yesterday?
-是的  -我是否有问你
- You did. - Did I ask you about
关于芝加哥警察暴力执法案件的事宜
police brutality cases in Chicago?
问了
You did.
那我是否有问你关于
And did I ask you for suggestions
如何解决这一问题的建议
on how to address this issue?
是的  你问了
Yes, you did.
而你选择不予回答
And you chose not to answer.
我不确定你的动机
I wasn't certain of your motives.
我的
My...
我的动机能有什么不对
What could be wrong with my motives?
我觉得你经常撒谎
I think you tend to lie.
你们律所靠警察暴力执法案件赚了很多钱
Your firm makes a lot of money on these police brutality cases.
这是提问吗
Is that a question?
是的
Yeah, it is.
"很多钱"是多少
Define "A lot of money."
占你们律所年收入的百分之三十
30% of its annual income.
我刚入职
Well, I'm new to the firm.
这种事情你还是问博斯曼先生比较好
I think it's best that you ask Mr. Boseman.
当我问你  你们律所如何看待
When I asked you about your firm's attitude
警察暴力执法时
about police brutality,
你是不是说问题在于
did you not say that the problem was
库克县人民仇视非裔美国人
the people of Cook County hated African-Americans?
需要我把问题复述一遍吗
Would you like me to repeat the question?
不
No.
是的
Yes.
当我问你
When I asked you
你们律所动机是否纯正时  你是不是说
if your firm's motives were pure, did you not say
问题在于库克县人民仇视非裔美国人
the problem is that Cook County hated African-Americans
且随意看待黑人生命
and treated black lives carelessly?
没有
No.
你没说过吗
You did not say that?
没有  我从未说过这样的话
No, I said nothing like it.
你的意思是我的会议记录并不正确吗
Are you saying that my notes from our meeting are incorrect?
你的会议记录错得一塌糊涂
Your notes on our meeting are bizarrely incorrect.
那你能告诉我这上面
Well, would you be kind enough to show me
哪里写错了
where I was mistaken?
你走进我的办公室
Well, you came into my office,
谈了谈设立你们专案组的性质
you explained the nature of your task force,
又说了你儿子的事情  然后就没了
we spoke about your son, and that was it.
我不清楚你是从哪里弄来的记录
I don't know where you got this quote,
但你说的  没有一个字
but there's not a single word of it
是准确的
that is accurate.
是吗
Really?
我们有谈到我儿子吗
And we spoke about my son?
为什么会谈到我儿子
Why would we speak about my son?
我问他近况如何
I asked you how he was.
我那已经去世的儿子
My son who died?
你...居然问他近况如何
You... asked me how he was?
是的  我不知道他已经过世了
Yes. I didn't know that he had passed.
我在你办公室呆了多久
How long was I in your office?
大概有六分钟
Six minutes, approximately.
你是说我把这其中的大部分时间
And you're saying that I spent the majority of that time
都用来谈我儿子
talking about my son?
没错
Yes.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Yes.
他在给我们下套
He's setting us up.
为什么
Why?
他想要减少警察暴力执法案件的数量
He wants to reduce the number of police brutality cases,
但不是通过减少警察施暴
but not by reducing police brutality...
而是减少立案的数量
by reducing the number of cases.
他想让我们无法起诉
He wants to reduce us?
但这不可能  不是吗
But he can't, can he?
你那个助理联邦检察官怎么说
What does your AUSA say?
他的确会说谎
Yeah, he lies.
你上司知道吗
Does your boss know that?
所有人都会说谎
Well, everyone lies.
但克里斯特瓦是对我们的事说谎
But Kresteva is lying about us.
他把子虚乌有的罪名强加给我们
He's saying we said things that we didn't.
好吧  我只能这样帮你
All right, here's what I can do.
我能帮你和助理总检察长威尔伯·丁肯
I could argue your case to the assistant attorney general,
说一下这件事
Wilbur Dincon.
他掌控克里斯特瓦的日程
He controls Kresteva's agenda.
你是认真的吗
You're serious?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
我也不知道
I don't know.
你太善良了
You're being nice.
我正喝着酒
Well, I'm drinking.
我喝酒时就善良
I'm nice when I drink.
是吗
Really?
我可坏了
I'm mean.
要来我家吗
You want to go back to my place?
-不要  -为什么
- No. - Why?
这看起来会像是在做交易
That would make this seem like a quid pro quo,
你不会希望变成那样的
and you don't want that.
-为什么啊  -因为
- Why don't I want that? - Because,
这是我第一次觉得你是个好人
for the first time, you seem like a good guy.
别毁了它
Don't ruin it.
不管怎么说
Anyway,
这也算一次奶昔之约了
we have a date for a milkshake.
该死  真不想当好人
Fuck, I hate being a good guy.
可以继续了
You may continue.
谢谢您  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.
诺伍德医生  我们来谈谈这个胚胎
Dr. Norwood, let's turn to this embryo.
请稍等   法官阁下
Excuse me, Your Honor.
诺伍德下周也要去英国
Norwood is going to England next week, too.
跟海特一家一样
Just like the Haights.
律师  你还有什么要问这名证人的吗
Counselor, do you have something more for this witness?
是的
Yes, I do.
你下周是不是要去英国  诺伍德医生
Are you traveling to England next week, Dr. Norwood?
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
问医生的个人行程有那么重要吗
Are the doctor's travel arrangements really necessary?
我不知道  重要吗
I don't know. Are they?
-重要  法官阁下  -重要
- They are, Your Honor. - They are.
你去英国  是要把这个胚胎
Are you going to England to implant
植入海特女士体内吗
this embryo into Mrs. Haight?
-是的  -为什么是在英国
- Yes. - And why in England?
而不是在美国
Why not in America?
英国批准这种手术的实施
Well, it's a procedure that's approved of in England.
所以这一手术在美国属非法吗
So this is a procedure that is illegal in America?
话倒不至于这么说
I wouldn't put it that way.
那你会怎么说呢
What way would you put it?
在美国还没有获批
It's not approved of in America.
好  你不如详细解释一下这个手术吧
Okay, well, why don't you explain this procedure.
海特夫人携带亚急性坏死性脑脊髓病遗传标记
Mrs. Haight has the genetic marker for Leigh syndrome.
这是一种会导致新生儿死亡的
It's a severe neurological disorder that results
严重的神经障碍疾病
in the death of the child.
英国允许实施的治疗方法
The procedure considered permissible in England
叫做DNA线粒体替换法
is called mitochondrial DNA replacement.
那是什么
What is that?
请用最简单平实的语言
And, please, explain it to me like
解释给我听
I'm an eight-year-old.
萨勒诺女士的胚胎
Ms. Salano's embryo
没有亚急性坏死性脑脊髓病的迹象  很健康
has no trace of Leigh's syndrome; it's clean.
我们从她的胚胎中提取基因
We take genes from that embryo
再把那些基因植入新的受精卵
and place those genes in a new fertilized egg...
这个胚胎是海特夫人的
the embryo belonging to Mrs. Haight.
这样海特夫人就有了一枚没有
In that way, Mrs. Haight has an embryo
亚急性坏死性脑脊髓病的胚胎
without Leigh's syndrome.
那第一个胚胎会怎样
What happens with the first embryo?
萨勒诺女士的胚胎
That one, Ms. Salano's embryo,
会做出遗传贡献  就是这样
is used for its genetic contribution, that's all.
然后它就被毁掉了
Then it's destroyed?
它没有被毁掉  而是无法再用于生育了
It's not destroyed. It's no longer viable.
他们不想要我的孩子
They don't want my baby.
只是想用我的一部分基因
They just want to use some of my genes
来使他们的孩子健康完整
to make their baby whole?
女士  请让你的律师来质询
Please, ma'am, let your lawyers ask the questions.
你可以回答她的问题吗  医生
Can you answer her question, Doctor?
问题不在于是谁的孩子
It's not a question of this baby or that.
当下的一切都只是可能性
Everything is a potentiality at this point.
海特夫妇的潜在胚胎需要植入
The Haights' potential embryo needs to be made whole
另一枚胚胎的遗传物质  才是完整的
with the genetic material from this other embryo.
所以你们通过拿走她的胚胎  攫取基因
So you would destroy Laura's chance of creating life
剥夺了劳拉孕育生命的机会
by taking her embryo and raiding it for its genes?
我不喜欢"攫取"这个词
I don't like the word "Raiding."
好的  我明白了
Okay, I get it.
我们现在讨论的内容是合同法的特殊领域
We are in some very odd areas of contract law now.
不  这事关生命  法官阁下
No, this is about life, Your Honor.
事实上并不是
Actually, no.
现存的胚胎是财产
The existing embryo is property.
唯一的问题就是
The only question is:
它的所有权属于谁
who does it belong to?
是萨勒诺女士还是海特先生
Does Ms. Solano own it or Mr. Haight?
你们明天呈上证据  我们再判决
You bring me evidence tomorrow, and we'll decide.
天呐  我讨厌这样
Oh, God, I hate this.
怎么了
Okay, so what?
雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯达律所
The law firm Reddick, Boseman & Kolstad
感到愤愤不平
is feeling aggrieved.
他们觉得专案组在不公平地针对他们
They feel like the task force is unfairly targeting them.
我猜这说的是我
I guess that means me.
是的  我觉得是这样
Yeah, I guess it does.
你在针对他们吗  迈克
Are you targeting them, Mike?
不  我针对的是警察暴力执法
No, I'm targeting police brutality.
通过针对起诉这类案件最多的律所
By targeting the law firm suing the most?
没错  这将会是统计数据上最伟大的进步
That's right. It'll show the greatest progress for the stats.
我不知道这有什么不妥  科林
I'm not sure what the problem is here, Colin.
迈克有他的策略  他需要实施它
Mike's got a strategy. He needs to pursue it.
我只是在担心这家律所的雇员都是非裔美国人
I'm just worried that it's an all African-American firm.
都是黑人
It's all black?
并非都是黑人
It's not all black.
戴安·洛哈特是白人
Diane Lockhart is Caucasian.
去针对一家雇员全是非裔美国人的律所
It just seems like it would be a public relations disaster
似乎会给公共关系带来灾难
to go after an all African-American firm.
尤其是试图阻止起诉警察暴力执法
Especially to try to curb police brutality suits.
我们不仅是因为警察暴力执法案件而针对他们
We're not just after them for police brutality.
还因为什么
Okay, what else?
我在寻找线索
I'm developing leads.
要么快点找
Well, develop them fast,
要么放弃
or drop it.
你有很多回报更丰厚的目标
You have a lot juicer targets.
是  先生  谢谢
Yes, sir. Thank you.
这是假新闻
It's fake news.
关于我的文章
The articles about me?
没错  骗点击率的
Yes. It's click bait.
大家对你父母的庞氏骗局不满
People are angry about your parents' Ponzi scheme,
所以这类文章有很多读者
so there's an audience for these kind of articles.
这是我前男友做的吗
It's from my ex-boyfriend?
可能来自另一个网络机器人
Probably from another bot.
它引用了你发布的被解雇的推文
It quotes your tweets about being fired...
不是我发布的  是假推特发的
Not mine. The fake tweets.
对  它把那些推文重新包装
Right. It repackages those tweets
并引用在文章中
and quotes them in an article.
所以  我们怎么阻止这件事
So, I mean, how do we stop this?
这是什么
What is this?
临限令
A T.R.O.
什么
A what?
临时限制令
A temporary restraining order.
库克县巡回法庭签发的
By order of the Cook County Circuit Court,
你必须立刻停止发布
you must immediately cease generating false news
关于玛娅·林德尔的假新闻
about Maia Rindell
直到就此案召开听证会
until a hearing can be held on the merits of her case against you.
你不怎么懂电脑吧
You don't know much about computers, do you?
-我懂的足够用了  -库克县巡回法庭
- I know enough. - Cook County Circuit Court
只对伊利诺伊州有管辖权
has jurisdiction only in Illinois.
我的加密软件通过美国20个州
I bounce my encrypted software through servers in 20 states,
墨西哥和日本的服务器运行
Mexico and Japan.
库克县巡回法庭无权强制执行这项命令
Cook County Circuit Court can't enforce this order.
无管辖权
No jurisdiction.
我们被法律制度限制住了
We've hit the limits of the legal system.
你是说我们束手无策了吗
You're telling me there's really nothing we can do?
-没有合法方式  -等等  你是想告诉我
- Not legally. - Wait, you trying to tell me
有什么不合法的办法吗
there's something I can do illegally?
不是
No.
-我听着就是这个意思  -我也是
- Sounded like that to me. - Me, too.
好了  这种事我不能参与
Okay, look, I can't be a party to whatever this is.
我得走了
I have to go.
你们有什么想法吗
Do you have any ideas?
新消息  来自布莱恩
老兄  真的假的
儿童摄像师制作幼童色情系列动画
亲爱的
Sweetheart, hi.
慢点说
Hey, just slow down.
当然是假的  老天
Of course it's not real. Jesus!
这种问题你还用问我
How could you even ask me that?
好了  关键词"妓女"  "肛栓"  "BDSM"
Here we go. Keywords: "Hooker," "Butt plug" And "BDSM."
还有吗
Anything else?
"束缚"怎么样
How about "Leash"?
完美
Perfect.
你来发送吧
You want to do the honors?
这不是真的
It's not true.
全都是假的
None of this stuff is true.
孩子  你得处理好这事
Son, you got to take care of this.
-都已经传开了  -都是假的  罗杰
- It's right here. - That's fake news, Roger.
我不在乎是什么  我脸书首页都是这个
I don't care what it is; it was on my Facebook page.
"酒品店4.5万美元神秘失踪"
"$45,000 missing from liquor store."
这根本说不通
That doesn't even make sense...
我在这工作  又不在酒品店工作
I work here, I don't work at a liquor store.
但是你的名字和照片  你看
But it's your name and your picture. Look.
罗杰  这随便一个黑客都能做到  我也能
Roger, any hacker could do that; I could do that.
别开除我
Please don't let me go.
你得去找警方谈谈  泰德
You got to go talk to the police, Ted.
据说他们正在找你
It says that they're looking for you.
海特先生  当诺伍德医生
Mr. Haight, when Dr. Norwood
找到吻合胚胎后  你就付了治疗的费用
found this matching embryo, and you paid for the treatment,
你付了多少钱
how much did you pay?
总共九千美金
All in, $9,000.
你付钱的时候
And when you paid that amount,
有没有怀疑过这个卵子
did you have any reason to believe that that egg
并不属于芝加哥理工大学
didn't belong to Chicago Poly-Tech?
-没有  -法官阁下
- No. - Your Honor,
我的当事人受到"无辜购买方"规则的保护
my clients are protected by the "Innocent purchasers" doctrine.
即便卵子本不该抵达芝加哥理工大学
Even if that egg shouldn't have arrived at Chicago Poly-Tech,
我的当事人也是合法公平地进行购买
it was purchased legally and fairly by my clients.
洛哈特女士  你有何回应
Ms. Lockhart, how do you respond?
法官阁下
Your Honor,
如果是我当事人的车被偷了
if my client's car were stolen
海特一家要征求你的允许...
and the Haights were asking your permission...
我的天
Oh, dear God.
律师  这不是被盗车辆
Counselor, this is not a stolen car.
不是什么东西都能够拿来类比的
At a certain point, analogy fails us.
我很反感我居然要用物权法
I'm disgusted that I have to use property law
来裁定生命的归属问题
to decide issues of life.
但是
But...
"无辜购买方"规则适用于本案
the "Innocent purchaser" doctrine holds.
胚胎属于海特一家
The embryo belongs to the Haights.
我很抱歉  非常抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你毁了我的生活
You're ruining my life.
出去  泰德
Get out of here, Ted.
否则我报警了
I'll call the cops.
你报啊  你真是个贱人  玛娅
Yeah, just try it. You are such a bitch, Maia.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你有什么想告诉我们的吗
Is there something you want to tell us?
跟你无关
This isn't about you.
事实上  如果与玛娅有关  就与我有关
Actually, if it's about Maia, it's about me.
你还想说什么吗
Anything else you want to say?
你撤下那些文章  我就把我的撤掉
You drop your news articles, and I'll drop mine.
好
Okay.
你可以走了
Your business is done here.
谢谢你  博斯曼先生
Thank you, Mr. Boseman.
不客气
No problem.
在这家律所  我们会为同伴挺身而出  玛娅
At this firm, we stand up for each other, Maia.
你还好吧
You all right?
她简直伤心欲绝
She was pretty inconsolable.
我知道
I know.
打击太大了
It's tough.
你后悔不生孩子吗
Do you regret not having children?
有时候会
Sometimes.
不常有
Not often.
有时候是什么时候
When are the sometimes?
跟我丈夫在一起的时候
With my husband.
现在我们想生太迟了  但是...
I mean, it's too late for us now, but, uh...
有时候看着他时我会想
I look at him and I wonder what...
他的儿子会是什么样的
you know, what his son would be like.
我女儿会是什么样的
Or my daughter.
说来有趣
Yeah. It's interesting.
大多说人认为我不想要孩子
Most people think I didn't want kids,
所以工作成了我生活的全部
and that's why I made my work my life.
但他们不知道的是  事实恰恰相反
What they don't realize, it's... it's really just the opposite.
是啊
Yes.
工作
Work.
工作让一切有意义
It's what gives it all meaning.
但唯一不同的是
The only difference is...
孩子活得比你长
kids survive you.
这并不总是件好事
That's not always a good thing.
库尔特
你还好吗  洛哈特女士
You all right, Ms. Lockhart?
英国
England.
人类受精与胚胎管理局
The Human Fertilisation & Embryology Authority?
英国的生育监管部门
Britain's fertility watchdog.
-你给他们打电话了  -是的
- And you called them? - We did.
怎么做到的
How?
我们拨打了区号44  然后拨了电话号
We dialed 44 and then the number.
我是问你们到底是怎么
I mean how in the hell did you manage
把他们牵扯进来的
to drag them into this?
不同的国家有不同的规则
Different country, different rules apply.
英国法律规定卵子的售价
British law says you can't sell your eggs
不能高于750英镑
for more than 750 pounds.
劳拉却将她的卵子卖了两万美元
Laura sold hers for $20,000.
所以你把我们搞惨了
So you just fucked us over.
根据英国法律  这些卵子的销售是无效的
Under British law, the sale of these eggs is invalid.
这有什么区别吗  法官阁下
What difference does that make, Your Honor?
您都已经对这个胚胎的所有权作出判决了
You've already ruled on the ownership of the embryo.
为了将它带到英国进行手术
For the express purpose of taking it to England for this procedure,
而这如今是被禁止的
which they have now been forbidden from doing.
尼古拉斯·海特  考特妮·海特  就我理解
Nicholas Haight, Courtney Haight, I, uh, take it
你们不会再前往英国了对吗
that your sojourn to England is no longer happening?
没错  法官阁下
That is correct, Your Honor.
你的当事人想要如何处理胚胎
And what do your clients want to do with the embryo?
他们想要销毁它
They would like to have it destroyed.
让我
Let-let me, uh,
想想能否找到你们律师喜欢的表达方法
see if I can put this in a way that you lawyers will like.
你的当事人买了一辆偷来的车
Your clients bought a stolen car,
而现在  不去让
and now, rather than see it
它的合法车主驾驶它
driven by its rightful owner,
他们想要丢弃销毁它
they want to bring it to the dump and flatten it.
是海特先生提供了受精卵的精子
Mr. Haight fertilized the egg.
这胚胎有一半属于他  他不想要这个小孩
It's half his. He doesn't want this child.
但我想要
But I do,
法官阁下
Your Honor.
好的
Right.
这就是分歧所在
And there's the rub.
你的当事人不需要这个胚胎  霍夫女士
Your clients have no use for this embryo, Ms. Hoff.
萨勒诺女士唯一能
Ms. Salano's only chance
拥有一个小孩的机会就是得到这个胚胎
of conceiving a child is with that same embryo.
所以胚胎判给她
So it's hers.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的天  谢谢你
Oh, my God, thank you.
我并不觉得我是一个情绪化的人
I did not think that I was an emotional person,
但看看我
but look at me.
这就是个很牵动情绪的事
It's an emotional thing.
不好意思
Excuse me.
如果我能怀孕的话  我只是想让你们知道
If I'm able to get pregnant, I just want you to know
这是你们的功劳
that it will be because of you.
这个小孩也是你们的
This child is just as much yours.
所以  如果你们想要参与我孩子的人生
So, please, if you want to play a role in my child's life,
我愿意尽我所能使其成为现实
I would do anything to make that a reality.
这个小孩需要懂得什么是爱
This child needs to know love.
滚蛋吧你
Fuck you.
林德尔的女儿花费35万美元狂购珠宝
看啊  他还在发这些文章
Look, he's still sending them out.
看啊
Look, there.
-不  这不是他  -这就是他
- No, it's not him. - Yes, it's him.
这是同一篇文章
I mean, it's the same article.
他说过他会停手的  但他没有
He said he was gonna stop, but he hasn't.
不  他停手了
No, he has.
-这些不是他写的  -你在说什么
- These aren't him. - What are you talking about?
我一直留意红迪网的帖子
I've been going on Reddit.
他们正在接手你前男友的工作
They're picking up what your ex-boyfriend dropped.
你和你的家庭在那里不受欢迎
You and your family are not liked there.
天哪
Oh, dear God.
等等  那我该做什么
Wait, so what do I do?
这些文章都发表出来了
I mean, these articles are out there.
讲着恶心的话
They say disgusting things.
这可是红迪网  那就是群乌合之众
It's Rreddit; that's, like, the teeming masses.
-你什么也别做  -什么  我不能起诉吗
- You don't do anything. - What, I can't sue?
-我不能  -你要这么做
- I can't... - Uh, here's what you do:
想知道吗
You want to know?
随它去吧
You let it go.
-不  我  -不  我是认真的
- Oh, no, I... - No, seriously.
你就随它去  不去管它
You have to let it go, ignore it,
不去想它
push it out of your mind.
认识你的人  都会懂你
The people who know you, know you.
知道你不会做这些事的
And they know you wouldn't do this.
你要相信这一点
Come on, you have to trust that.
我们的指控很清楚了
Our charge is clear.
跟雷迪克&博斯曼律所的
It's not about police brutality
暴力执法案件无关
with Reddick & Boseman.
他们做了什么
What have they done?
他们的律师做了什么
What have their lawyers done?
就是这里
Here we go.
这是一篇新闻
Here's a news article
写的是关于雷迪克&博斯曼的一位律师的事
about one of the Reddick & Boseman lawyers now.
她花了35万美元
She just spent $350,000
买珠宝
on jewelry.
这些钱是哪来的
Where did that money come from?
谁给她的
Who gave it to her?
现在  各位  我们行动起来
Now, come on, people, let's go.
看我们能挖出什么来
Let's see what we can dig up!
行动起来
Come on!